Let's assume you were recently hired by a Start-up. On the first day, you meet the CEO and are given an assignment. Your CEO has decided that all products will be named according to the following pattern.

Your CEO calls the pattern “P@tter”. Two product names obey P@tter if they are permutations of each other, ignoring spaces and capitalization.

Your task is to determine whether two product names obey P@tter.
Input description/format

The input will consist of two product names per line, in quotation marks, which are not part of the names. The quoted names will be separated by a comma and potentially whitespace.
You can assume that there will be ≤ 1000 lines in the input file. Also, product name length will be ≤ 255 characters and product names will contain only ASCII characters.
Output description/format

For each line of input, output the result in one of the following 2 ways (case sensitive):

    Valid Pattern
    Invalid Pattern

Example input

"Calculate", "Acute Call"
"Drop Cue" , "Cued Pro"
"carE Not", "raCe On"

Example output

Valid Pattern
Valid Pattern
Invalid Pattern